audinate.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Audinate

Audinate Group Limited (ACN 618 616 916) and its subsidiaries ("Audinate", "we" or "us") have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to protect the privacy of the individuals with whom we deal and comply with applicable privacy laws. Audinate respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information (being information that identifies you, or reasonably identifies you) that you share with us. Generally, you can browse through our website without giving us any information about yourself.

When we do need your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information. By providing us your personal information you consent to us collecting, holding, using and disclosing your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. You may choose not to give your personal information to us. However, if you choose not to give us your personal information we may not be able to provide our services to you. 

### The personal information we collect and how we collect it

We collect information about you and your interaction with us, for example, when you purchase or use any of our products or services, call us or visit our website. The types of personal information/personal data that we collect directly from you may include (but is not limited to) your identity, contact details, IP address, job title and the industry in which you work When you make a purchase on our website, your credit card information may be collected, but that information is sent directly and securely to credit card processors and it is our policy that such information is not stored on our servers.

Whenever it is reasonable and practicable to do so we will collect information about you directly from you. However, we may also collect information about you (including personal information) from other sources including publically available sources such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn profiles, company websites, online directories and/or third parties. marketing automation platforms like Hubspot, customer relationship management (CRM) platforms like Salesforce.com, and data cleansing and augmentation third parties such as Data.com, industry trade publications and other professional associations. No matter whether we collect your personal information directly from you or from/via third parties, we will use, manage, hold and disclose your personal information in accordance with the applicable privacy laws and this privacy policy.

Some of the ways we may collect personal and non-personal information from you include via websites, by subscribing to our services through our registration forms, cookies, or pixel tags (web beacons). A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of our website may use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of the Audinate website if you do so. In particular, you may be required to accept cookies in order to complete certain actions on our website. You do not need to have cookies turned on, however, to use/navigate through many parts of our website, except access to certain of our web pages may require a login and password.

A pixel tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel, and may be associated with cookies on the visitors’ hard drives. Pixel tags allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of  our website , to deliver branded services, to serve ads, and to help determine the effectiveness of promotional or advertising campaigns. When used in HTML-formatted e-mail messages, pixel tags can tell the sender whether and when the e-mail has been opened.

We also may collect other personal information and data that you might submit to our websites,  or as you access other related third-party sites for registration for training and events, webinars,  participation in surveys, contests, promotions, or other related Audinate activities or events,  apply for a job, request customer support, or communicate with us via third party social media  sites.

### How that information is used

We collect, hold and use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * to provide the requested products and/or services to you;
  * to investigate and respond to claims from you;
  * to contact you, for example, to respond to your queries or complaints or if we need to tell you something important;
  * to provide bulletins and updates pertaining to your products
  * to comply with our legal obligations and assist government and law enforcement agencies or regulators
  * for research and feedback on product development;
  * to tailor your experience on our website, and to direct you to content we believe will be of interest to you.
  * However, in each marketing email message you will be provided with the ability to opt out from receiving future marketing messages.

We may use non-personal information for the following purposes:

  * to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction, so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future; and
  * to enable third-party advertising companies, such as Google AdSense and AdRoll, to use your browsing history to show Audinate ads on other sites throughout the internet.

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

### How do we store and hold personal information?

We store most information about you in computer systems and databases operated by either us or our external service providers. Some information about you is recorded in paper files that we store securely.

We take all practicable steps to protect your personal information from misuse, interference, loss, unauthorised or accidental access, and modification, processing, erasure or disclosure

We will also take reasonable steps to destroy or de-identify personal information once we no longer require it for the purposes for which it was collected or for any secondary purpose permitted.

### Who we disclose that information to

Audinate may disclose your personal information to other Audinate offices or subsidiaries which are located outside of Australia, in the United States, United Kingdom, and Hong Kong.

We may also disclose personal information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this privacy policy:

  * to external service providers so that they may perform services for us or on our behalf;
  * to resellers and distributors of Audinate products when it is necessary to share information for the purposes of facilitating that business relationship;
  * when an event or marketing activity is co-sponsored by manufacturers, resellers, distributors, or professional association partners, we may provide the specific registration information you provided to participate in that activity to the co-sponsors;
  * where we are required or authorized by law to do so;
  * when we are permitted to disclose the information under applicable privacy laws;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Audinate or others;
  * in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company; or to any of our related companies including our current and future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries, and other companies under common control and ownership;
  * or when you have expressly consented to the disclosure or such consent may reasonably be inferred from the circumstances.

Where a disclosure is made to a third party for the purposes of processing your personal information on our behalf, we will ensure by using contractual or other means that disclosed personal information is (i) not kept at the data processor/service provider for longer than is necessary for the purpose of processing the information/providing the service to us and (ii) protected from unauthorised or accidental access, processing, erasure, loss or use.

We also may share non-personal information with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

### Communications

Unless you have indicated otherwise, opted-out or it is prohibited by applicable laws, we will use your personal information to offer you products and services we believe may be of interest to you. You may opt-out of receiving these communications from Audinate by following the instructions in those communications or by contacting us at the contact details provided below. If you opt-out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about our ongoing business relations or product updates specific to products you have purchased or licensed.

### Keeping information accurate and up to date

We take reasonable steps to ensure that all information we hold is as accurate as is possible. You are able to contact us at any time (via the contact details below) and request access to the personal information we hold about you or ask for its correction.

There is no charge for requesting access to your personal information but we reserve the right to require you to meet our reasonable costs in providing you with access (such as photocopying costs or costs for time spent on collating large amounts of material or postage charges).

We will respond to your requests to access or correct personal information in a reasonable time. In most circumstances, we will allow you access to your personal information, however, access may be refused where we are permitted by law to refuse such access. If we refuse your request to access your personal information, we will provide reasons to you.

### Links

Audinate cannot guarantee or accept responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of websites to which we provide links.

### Complaints

If you have a complaint about how we have collected, used or disclosed your personal information, or if we have not corrected or provided you access to your personal information, then you may contact us at our contact details below to ask questions or make a complaint.

We will consider your complaint and determine whether it requires further investigation. We will notify you of the outcome of this investigation and any subsequent internal investigation.

If you remain unsatisfied with the way in which we have handed a privacy issue, you may approach an independent advisor or contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner for guidance ([www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/)). 

If you don’t want the advertising you see on the internet to be tailored to your browsing, you may opt-out of interest-based advertising from the third-party services that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) [here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices). Google and AdRoll are members of the NAI. Visit the [NAI site](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) for more detail.

### Changes to the privacy policy

Please continue to check our privacy policy regularly for any changes. From time to time, we may change our policy on how we handle personal information or the types of personal information which we hold. Any changes to our policy will be published on our website. You may obtain a copy of our current policy from our website or by contact us at the details below.

By providing additional personal information or continuing to use our services after we have notified you of changes to our privacy policy you will be deemed to have accepted those changes to our privacy policy.

### Contact Details

<https://www.audinate.com/contact/marketing>
